# Jithendra Maremanda

• 10-2-449/2/2,sri ram nagar colony,vidyanagar, karimnagar

**≥** jithendramaremanda@gmail.com

+91 7075114405

in https://www.linkedin.com/in/jithendra-maremanda-761903230/

https://github.com/Jithendra-maremanda

### **Profile**

I am Associate at the Mashreq Global services, and worked as Intern in Atelia software Company as a Front-End Developer with less than 1 year of internship experience in Education, Employee Management, healthcare Demonstrated leadership abilities and team work skills as well as the ability to accomplish tasks under minimal direction and supervision.

## **Professional experience**

Professional ex	perience
01/2024 – present Bangalore, India	<ul> <li>Associate, Mashreq Global services</li> <li>I am working as associate at the Mashreq Global services</li> <li>Having the 8 months of experience in the banking and payment domain</li> </ul>
Internship	
01/2023 - 04/2023	<ul> <li>Trainee Software Engineer, LegalCraft Solutions Private Limited</li> <li>Learn mobile application and web development technology Skills</li> <li>And solved some common issues in the Application</li> <li>Design the UI for Mobile Application</li> <li>Implement various sample projects with dart and flutter</li> </ul>
2021 - 07/2022	<ul> <li>Front-End Developer Intern, Atelia Software</li> <li>Developed frontend user interface and features in the Application using Flutter.</li> <li>Implemented features like Doctor.</li> <li>Appointment, Doctor Profile, Patient Scheduling, Vitals Monitoring etc</li> <li>Technologies: Dart, Flutter</li> </ul>
Education	
09/2022 – 07/2022	<ul> <li>CCBP Intensive 4.0 Tech Program</li> <li>Full Stack Web Development</li> <li>CCBP intensive is an Industry Ready Certification program focus on full stack web development that</li> <li>provides training through an immersive hands-on and reverse-engineered curriculum.</li> </ul>
07/2018 - 07/2022	<ul> <li>Under Graduation: BTech</li> <li>Sasi Institute of Technology and Engineering College, Tadepalligudem, AP</li> <li>Electronics and Communication Engineering</li> </ul>
05/2016 – 05/2018	<ul><li>Intermediate:</li><li>Sri Gayatri Junior College, Karimangar, Ts</li><li>Mathematics, Physics, Chemistry</li></ul>
04/2016	SSC • Paramita Lerner's Foundation, Karimnagar, TS



HTML CSS Bootstrap JavaScript Tailwindcss Python Flutter React Js

SOL

## **Projects**

**Book Hub using React js,** Book Hub creating an app that will fetch data from an internal server using a class component, displaying that data, using component lifecycle methods, routing concepts, authentication, and authorization, and adding responsiveness to the website.

**Technologies**: HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, Javascript, ReactJS

- fetch data from an internal server using a class component lifecycle methods
- routing, authentication

Link:jithendra2000.ccbp.tech/login ∂

#### **Todos Application**

Technologies: HTML, CSS, JS, Bootstrap

- Displayed list of todos with HTML list elements, styled todo list using CSS, Bootstrap Implemented todo crud operations by using JavaScript event listeners and updated UI dynamically by
- using JavaScript DOM operations.

Used Arrays, Objects and their methods during todolist CRUD Operations, Persisted todo list state on page reloads using local storage methods.

Link:jithendra54613.ccbp.tech ∂

Food Munch Website, Created a static responsive website which is comfortable in all smart devices

Technologies: HTML, CSS, Bootstrap Flex-Grid System

- Developed User friendly application
- Implemented Delivery and Payment and Explore menu Sections

**Link:**https://jithend3641321.ccbp.tech/ *⊗* 

**Tourism Website**, Created a static website that enables the user to browse through the content.

**Technologies**: HTML, CSS, Bootstrap

- Developed mobile-first layout using Bootstrap flex and CSS box model
- Implemented Navigation via Carousal point

Link:jithendra1649.ccbp.tech ∂

#### **Certificates**

- I Obtained a Certification AMCAT Certified Software Development Trainee from Aspiring Minds
- I completed successfully NPTEL Certificate on Technical English for engineers.
- Successfully Certified in "Improve Your Communication Skills" Specialization courses in Coursera.

#### Achievements

#### **Activities**

- I have participated in the IEEE Presentation on Bermuda triangle
- I actively performed as volunteer in Freshers day event in our college
- I stood as runner in body building competition in our college.

#### **Declaration**

I hereby declare that the details and information given above are complete and true to the best of my knowledge